Guide to the Records of Office of the Vice President for External Affairs and the Office of the Vice President for University Relations, John J. O'Connor RG.7.2
New York University Archives
- Series I. Administrative Files, 201841
  - Naomi Levine, Jul 1983-Aug 1983; 201902 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Loeb, Mar 1989; 201901 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Jill Long, Jun 1986; 201900 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - London Bus, Mar 1988; 201899 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Mailick Project, Mar 1983-May 1983; 201898 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Manville Trust Fund, Oct 1989; 201897 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Maragall, Pascual (Mayor of Barcelona), Jun 1989; 201896 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Marnold Fellow, Nov 1987; 201895 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Mayoral Debates Program, Jul 1989Aug 1989; 201894 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Macintosh, Aug 1984; 201893 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Medicare (Catastrophic Illness), Feb 1987; 201892 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Medical Center, Biomedical Research Building, Sep 1987-Oct 1987; 201891 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Medical Research Training, Mar 1987; 201890 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Mitterand Visit, Jan 1989-Feb 1989; 201889 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Matt Miller, Apr 1987; 201888 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Mondale for President, Jun 1983-Sep 1983; 201887 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - National Public Service Program, Feb 1986; 201886 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - National Arts Education Research Center, Sep 1987; 201885 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Anthropology Journal, Jun 1983; 201884 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - New York Stock Exchange, Jun 1983; 201883 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - NYU "bio", Apr 1989; 201882 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - NYU club, Mar 1989; 201881 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - NYU Magazine (1 of 2), Nov 1985-Feb 1991; 201880 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - NYU Magazine (2 of 2), Nov 1985-Feb 1991; 232497 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - NYU Magazine, Distribution, 1989; 201879 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - New York University Press, Jan 1985-Sep 1991; 201878 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - NYU Report, Jun 1987-Aug 1987; 201877 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Operating Budget, Jun 1988; 201876 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - New Boston Group, Nov 1988; 201875 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Estate of Arthur M. Apman, Nov 1987; 201874 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - RW Johnson Foundation, Jun 1989; 201873 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Palm Beach, Jan 1984; 201872 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Pell Grant, Apr 1986; 201871 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Handicap Education, Jul 1985; 201870 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Polish People's Republic, Sep 1987; 201869 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Political Leaders, Jun 1983-Aug 1983; 201868 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Plaque, Nov 1986; 201867 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Salomon Lecture, Sep 1982; 201866 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Schaetzel, Robert (former ambassador), Apr 1986; 201865 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Sherman Project, Oct 1986; 201864 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Singapore University, May 1989; 201863 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Silverman, Henry, Aug 1987; 201862 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Simon & Schuster Student Travel Guide, Feb 1986-Mar 1986; 201861 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - 6 Year Report, May 1988; 201860 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Speech Writing, Jan 1984; 201859 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Super Conducting Supercollider, Jun 1987; 201858 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Tax Issues, Sep 1987; 201857 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Tiffany Torch, Feb 1987-Jul 1987; 201856 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Tisch Hospital, Feb 1989-Nov 1989; 201855 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Trustee Trips, Nov 1983-Feb 1988; 201854 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - UBIT, undated; 201853 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - University Senate, Nov 1989; 201852 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - University Newspaper, Sep 1987; 201851 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - US Information Agency, Mar 1987; 201850 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Vassiliou, George, Oct 1989; 201849 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Volcker, Paul, Jul 1987; 201848 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Wall Street Seminar, Jan 1984-Apr 1988; 201847 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Ward, Tom, Jan 1987-Jan 1988; 201846 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Muller, Jordan Weiss, Aug 1988; 201845 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Weslyan Consortium, Oct 1989; 201844 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Wiesel Dinner, Jun 1989; 201843 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Winter Celebration, Mar 1985; 201842 (Box 17, Folder 68)
- Addendum 7/5/2007, 201451
  - Alumni Counsel/ Alumni Federation resolution, undated; 201840 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Federation, ca.Sep 1981-Dec 1989, 1980-1987; 201839 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Relations, undated; 201838 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Today, undated; 201837 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Travel, undated; 201836 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, undated; 201835 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Trustees, undated; 201834 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Ambassador of Spain Gift Presentation, Mar 1990; 201833 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Americorps, undated; 201832 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Andreotti Convocation, Mar 1990; 201831 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Animal Research, undated; 201830 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Annual Fund, undated; 201829 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Annual Giving, undated; 201828 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Apartheid, undated; 201827 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Applications for Employment, undated; 201826 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Articles, undated; 201825 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Asbestos, undated; 201824 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - "Bates Must Play Campaign", undated; 201823 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Billion-dollar Campaign, undated; 201822 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Black Alumni Association, undated; 201821 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Black Alumni Association (ECR's)/ Giving Records, undated; 201820 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Black Lobby Day in Albany 1992, 201819 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Board of Trustees, undated; 201818 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Bobkin Lane, undated; 201817 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Bobkin Lane Café, undated; 201816 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Bobst Award, undated; 201815 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Book Benders, undated; 201814 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Bowen Event, undated; 201813 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Crime and Management Article on Lee Brown, undated; 201812 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - BSR, undated; 201811 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Budget, undated; 201810 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Budget, undated; 201809 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Budget Submissions, undated; 201808 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Buildings, undated; 201807 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Bundy Aid, undated; 201806 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Barbara Bush Convocation, undated; 201805 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Business Council of NYS Inc., undated; 201804 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Bid Business Improvement District, undated; 201803 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - CampusVision, undated; 201802 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - CAS, undated; 201801 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Casa Hispanica, undated; 201800 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Casa Italiana, undated; 201799 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Case Membership, undated; 201798 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Catholic Center, undated; 201797 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Center for War, Peace, and News Media, undated; 201796 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Challenge Funds, undated; 201795 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Charitable Deduction Guidelines, undated; 201794 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Charter and Bylaws, undated; 201793 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Child care, undated; 201792 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Choral Alumni Club, undated; 201791 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Cicu, undated; 201790 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Clinton/Gore, undated; 201789 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Coles/ Bobst, undated; 201788 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - College Savings Bank, undated; 201787 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Columbi Univ., undated; 201786 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Community Board Number 2, undated; 201785 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Community Fund, undated; 201784 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Community Health Services Subcommittee Minutes, undated; 201783 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Community Relations, undated; 201782 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Community Relations, 1990; 201781 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Community Relations, 1991; 201780 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Community Relations, 1992; 201779 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Computers, undated; 201778 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Computer Inventory Survey, undated; 201777 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Conflict of Interest, undated; 201776 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Construction, undated; 201775 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Contact Sheets, undated; 201774 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Creative Arts Team, undated; 201773 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Cuomo Executive Budget, undated; 201772 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Dental Clinic, undated; 201771 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Dentristry, College of, undated; 201770 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Dept. of Transportattion, undated; 201769 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Depositions, undated; 201768 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Desktop Publishing, undated; 201767 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Dining Services, undated; 201766 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Disposal Fee Committee, undated; 201765 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Domestic Partner Legislation, undated; 201764 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Dr. Janez Drnovsek, undated; 201763 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Stephen Dunn and Associates, undated; 201762 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Emergency Management System, undated; 201761 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Employment, 1990-1992; 201760 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Employment Brochure, undated; 201759 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Unititled, undated; 201758 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Europe, 1992; 201757 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Exchnage Student Program, undated; 201756 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - FAS, undated; 201755 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Faculty Research Network, 1989-1990; 201754 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Faculty Resource Network, 1989-1992; 201753 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Fax, undated; 201752 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Federal Relations, 1999; 201751 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Federal Relations, 1990-1992; 201750 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Council on Federal Relations, 1995-1997; 201749 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Fernandez Dinner, 1990; 201748 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Fiji, undated; 201747 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Financial Report, undated; 201746 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Fine Arts Institute, undated; 201745 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - First Presbyterian Church, undated; 201744 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Founders Day, 1992; 201743 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Freelancer, undated; 201742 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Fundraising Gift Acknowledgments, undated; 201741 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Gallatin, undated; 201740 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Government Affairs, 1990; 201739 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Government Relations, 1991; 201738 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Government Relations, 1990; 201737 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School of Business, undated; 201736 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Greek Cultural Center, undated; 201735 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Greenwich House Preschool, undated; 201734 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Greenwich Village, undated; 201733 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Grey Art Gallery, undated; 201732 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - GSAS Centennial File, undated; 201731 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Guest Housing, undated; 201730 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Guest Suites, undated; 201729 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Havel Convocation, undated; 201728 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Harvard Gazette, undated; 201727 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Hebrew Union College, undated; 201726 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Heritage Brass, undated; 201725 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Higher Education: Financing, undated; 201724 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Honorary Degree, undated; 201723 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - House of Representatives, undated; 201722 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Housing, undated; 201721 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Humanities, undated; 201720 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Chet Huntley Lectures, undated; 201719 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Indirect Costs, undated; 201718 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Info Center, undated; 201717 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Institute of East- West Business Dynamics, East European Parl. Program, undated; 201716 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Invitations Declined, undated; 201715 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Ireland House, undated; 201714 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Ireland House Dedication, 1993; 201713 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Italian Center, undated; 201712 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Milton Krents, undated; 201711 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - LAB Project, undated; 201710 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Law, School of, undated; 201709 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Office of Legal Counsel, undated; 201708 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Dr. Kenneth Eugene Lehrer, undated; 201707 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - L.G.O.'s Innauguration, undated; 201706 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Little Red School House, undated; 201705 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Low Level Waste Group, 1992; 201704 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - MBT, undated; 201703 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Medical Center, undated; 201702 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Medical Center/ Community Service, undated; 201701 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Mega-Cities, undated; 201700 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Mercer St., undated; 201699 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Midtown Community Court, undated; 201698 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Middle States Association, undated; 201697 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Minetta Lane, undated; 201696 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Musical Theatre Hall of Fame, undated; 201695 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - National Audubon Society, undated; 201694 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - National Commission on Independent Higher 1d, undated; 201693 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - NAICU, undated; 201692 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - National Science Foundation, undated; 201691 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - National Service Trust Fund, undated; 201690 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - NEA, undated; 201689 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Neural Science, 1986-1988; 201688 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Neural Science, 1989; 201687 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Neural Science, 1990-1992; 201686 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - New School for Social research, undated; 201685 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Articles, undated; 201684 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - New York City Parks, undated; 201683 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - New Yorker Club, undated; 201682 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - New York Festivals, 1992; 201681 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - New York Foundling Hospital, undated; 201680 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - New York State Assembly, undated; 201679 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - New York State Senate, undated; 201678 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - New York Times Reprint, undated; 201677 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - NYU Club, undated; 201676 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - NYU Today, undated; 201675 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - NYU Trolley, undated; 201674 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - NYU Tuition, undated; 201673 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - NYU in Washington, undated; 201672 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Notre Dame, undated; 201671 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - John J. O'Connor in Washington D.C., undated; 201670 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Ohio State University, undated; 201669 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Onassis, undated; 201668 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Onassis Center-Potential Donors, undated; 201667 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Onassis Convocation, undated; 201666 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Onassis Letters, undated; 201665 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Opportuntiy Fellow Program, undated; 201664 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - OSHA, undated; 201663 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Paintings, undated; 201662 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Party, undated; 201661 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Governor George Pataki, undated; 201660 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - The Evelynne Patterson Cookbook, undated; 201659 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Phone-a-thon, 1989; 201658 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Phone-a-thon, 1989-1992; 201657 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Photo Bureau, undated; 201656 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Playground, undated; 201655 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Postal Subsidies, undated; 201654 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Potential Speakers, undated; 201653 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Presidential Citations, undated; 201652 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - President's Undesignated Fund, undated; 201651 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Presidential Lecture Series, undated; 201650 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Presidents Research Caucus, undated; 201649 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Object Codes, 1993-1994; 201648 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Object Codes, 1993-1994; 201647 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Object Codes, 1994-1995; 201646 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Object Codes, 1994-1995; 201645 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Object Codes, 1989-1990; 201644 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Object Codes, 1990-1991; 201643 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Object Codes, 1991-1992; 201642 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Object Codes, 1992-1993; 201641 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Object Codes, 1992-1993; 201640 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Primerica, undated; 201639 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Printing/ Purchasing Guidelines, undated; 201638 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Protection, undated; 201637 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Provincetown, undated; 201636 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Publications Controls Guidelines, undated; 201635 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Radioactive Waste, undated; 201634 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Rectors Conference, undated; 201633 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Registration, undated; 201632 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Resume, undated; 201631 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Rhodes Scholarship, undated; 201630 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Root-Tilden-Snow Shcolarship Program, undated; 201629 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Ruggieri, undated; 201628 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Russian-American Press, undated; 201627 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Sandelman, Robert M., undated; 201626 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - SEC, undated; 201625 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - School of Social Work, undated; 201624 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Untitled, undated; 201623 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Security Locker Room, undated; 201622 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Security, undated; 201621 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - SEHNAP, undated; 201620 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Seed, undated; 201619 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Snow Dining Room, undated; 201618 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Space Allocations, undated; 201617 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Spain, undated; 201616 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - King of Spain, undated; 201615 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - King of Spain, 1983; 201614 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Spanish House, undated; 201613 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Special Events, 1983-1992; 201612 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - The C.V. Starr Center, undated; 201611 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - State Dental Aid, undated; 201610 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - State Officials, undated; 201609 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - State Relations, 1988-1989; 201608 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - States Relations, 1990; 201607 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Statue of Liberty, undated; 201606 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Stern School of Business, undated; 201605 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Student Affairs, undated; 201604 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Summer, undated; 201603 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Profess/ Doctor Rite Sussmuth (CDU), undated; 201602 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Sweeney Scholarship, undated; 201601 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Tax Exempt Financing, undated; 201600 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Teacher Effectiveness, undated; 201599 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Telecommunications, undated; 201598 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Ten Year Report, undated; 201597 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Thank You Letters, undated; 201596 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Third Avenue Dormitories, undated; 201595 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Thompson, Marilyn Berry, 1982-1986; 201594 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Thompson, Marilyn Berry, 1987; 201593 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Thompson, Marilyn Berry, 1987; 201592 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Thompson, Marilyn Berry, 1989; 201591 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Tisch, undated; 201590 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - TSOA, undated; 201589 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Traffic Light, undated; 201588 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Transfer of Funds, undated; 201587 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Triangle Shirtwaist, undated; 201586 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Trolley, undated; 201585 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Trustees, undated; 201584 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Tuition Remission, undated; 201583 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - 25 W. 4th St., undated; 201582 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Ultra Violet, undated; 201581 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Ultra Violet, undated; 201580 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - USA Union, undated; 201579 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - US Department of education, undated; 201578 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - US Department of Labor, undated; 201577 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - US News and World Reports, undated; 201576 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - United States Senate, undated; 201575 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - US Senators, undated; 201574 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - United Way, undated; 201573 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - UAA, undated; 201572 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - University Budget, undated; 201571 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - University Real Estate, undated; 201570 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Urban Development Corporation (UBC), undated; 201569 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - The Urban Institute, undated; 201568 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Vendors, undated; 201567 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Video, undated; 201566 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - The Village Alliance, undated; 201565 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - The Village Improvement Committee, undated; 201564 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - The Villager, undated; 201563 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - The Violet Ball, undated; 201562 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Voicemail, undated; 201561 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Arcady Ivanovich Volsky, undated; 201560 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Wagner School, undated; 201559 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Washington Place, undated; 201558 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Washington Square Arch, undated; 201557 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Washington Square Closing, undated; 201556 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Washington Square Coalition, undated; 201555 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Washington Square Park, undated; 201554 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Washingotn Square Village, undated; 201553 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Washington Workshops Foundation, undated; 201552 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Watch Team, undated; 201551 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Watch Team, 1992-1993; 201550 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Watch Team, 1993-1994; 201549 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Weehawken, undated; 201548 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Weehawken Sign Brochure and Picture, undated; 201547 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - T. G. White Find Awards for 1993, 201546 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Window Guards, undated; 201545 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Winter Garden Concert, undated; 201544 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Zerilli Merino, undated; 201543 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Jan-92, 1992-1992, 2001, undated; 201542 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Feb-92, 1992-1992; 201541 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Mar-92, 1992-1992; 201540 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Apr-92, 1992-1992; 201539 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - May-92, 1992-1992; 201538 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Dec-92, 1992-1992; 201537 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Nov-92, 1992-1992; 201536 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Oct-92, 1992; 201535 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Sep-92, 1992-1992; 201534 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Aug-92, 1992; 201533 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Jul-92, 1992; 201532 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Jan-94, 1994-1994; 201531 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Feb-94, 1994-1994; 201530 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Mar-94, 1994-1994; 201529 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Apr-94, 1994-1994; 201528 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - May-94, 1994-1994, undated; 201527 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Jun-94, 1994-1994; 201526 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Jul-94, 1994-1994; 201525 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Sep-94, 1994-1994; 201524 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Oct-94, 1994-1994; 201523 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Aug-94, 1994-1994; 201522 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Nov-94, 1994-1994; 201521 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Dec-94, 1994-1994; 201520 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Jan-95, 1995-1995; 201519 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Feb-95, 1995-1995; 201518 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Mar-95, 1995-1995; 201517 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Apr-95, 1995-1995; 201516 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - May-95, 1995-1995; 201515 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Jun-95, 1995-1995; 201514 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Jul-95, 1995-1995; 201513 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Aug-95, 1995-1995; 201512 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - JB Correspondence, 1990-1991; 201511 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - JB Correspondence, 1989-1990; 201510 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - JLO Correspondence, 1991-1993; 201509 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - JB Correspondence, 1991-1992; 201508 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - AAU, 1990-1994; 201507 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Admissions, 1990-1994; 201506 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Albany Day [empty], 1994-1994; 201505 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Albany [empty], 1995-1995; 201504 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Albany, 1992-1992; 201503 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Albany Day, 1993-1993; 201502 (Box 28, Folder 10)